AI DevCon is the conference [music] for
developers, technical leads, and
engineering leaders who are driving
their software development forward into
the agentic future.
This November, we're hosting our third
in-person conference, returning [music]
to New York City, where we'll be joined
by more than 700 in-person attendees and
3,000 virtual guests [music] from around
the world. 67% of our attendees are in
technical roles, 64% at [music] the lead
level or above, and 18% C-suite or
founder level. Our conference is [music]
powered by the AI native dev community,
home to over 70,000 developers who tune
into our podcast, attend in-person
meetups, and [music] watch our vibrant
YouTube channel.
Sponsoring AI DevCon will give you
direct access not only to the conference
attendees, but also let you tap into our
wider community. Sponsorship packages
start at just $7,000, but places are
strictly limited. [music]
Email sponsorships@tessel.io
to find out more.
We can't wait to have you join us in New
York.